

ANANDA AYU RAMADHANI

Medical Recorders

□ anandaayur12@gmail.com □ 085700288154 □ www.linkedin.com/in/ananda-ayu-59869b297 ♀ Pajangan Bantul, Yogyakarta

I am a fresh graduate from Gadjah Mada University, Health Information Management study program with good academic grades and good interpersonal skills. Have skills in service, communication, medical record audit, and disease coding analysis. These skills were acquired through internships. Teamwork and leadership skills gained from team project experience. Currently have an active STR

Experience

Internship (Medical Recorders) | RS PKU Muhammdiyah Yogyakarta - Yogyakarta

Juni 2023-Agustus 2023

- Serving patient administration in the outpatient registration section
- Serving patient administration in the inpatient registration section
- Analyzing the completeness of patient medical record files in the assembling section
- Inpatient medical record audit
- Analyzing the accuracy of disease and action codes
- Sorting medical record file forms according to established standards

Internship (Medical Recorders) | Puskesmas Kotagede II - Yogyakarta

Januari 2024-Februari 2024

- Serving patient administration in the registration
- Analyzing the completeness of patient medical record files returning from other units
- Quantitative analysis of medical record files
- Analyzing the accuracy of diagnosis codes in patient medical records

Other Experience | Youth Organization - Yogyakarta

April 2021-present

 As treasurer by carrying out several responsibilities, namely recording the income and expenditure of money, as well as making a cost budget plan

Education

Applied bachelor, health information management | Gadjah Mada University - Yogyakarta

Grade Point Average (GPA): 3,93

Projects

University Projects | - Developing Skills

- Project day to design an electronic medical record interface for problem solving patient medical record completeness
- Project day to design an electronic medical record interface to solve the problem of inaccurate diagnosis codes

Skills

Analysis of medical record - Advanced | Audit of medical record - Advanced | Communication - Advanced | Design Interface - Advanced | Teamwork - Advanced | Mastering ICD 10 and ICD 9 cm - Advanced | Problem Solving - Advanced | Time management - Advanced | Microsoft Office - Advanced

Languages

Indonesia - Proficient | English - Beginner